Guide to the New York University Collection of Contemporary Composers' Websites MSS.496
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Vincent, Jonathan, February 2015-ongoing; 2 websites in 2 archived websites.
  Crawl was limited to domains and subdomains of jonathanvincent.biz and jonathanvincent.co.uk in order to remain within the collection scope and data constraints.
- Weisman, Stefan, February 2014- ongoing; 1 websites in 1 archived website.
  Robots.txt (a piece of code designed to limit crawler activity within a website) was ignored. Crawl was limited to domains and subdomains of http://www.stefanweisman.com/ in order to remain within the collection scope and data constraints.
  Embedded Flash audio player files on the site were captured, but do not render in the archived copy. Future changes to the Wayback Machine may allow the files to be played.
  The website contains a biography of the artist, information about his compositions and projects, news and reviews about Weisman, examples of his prose works, a calendar of his events, a discography of his published albums, and examples of his works in the form of embedded audio files. The compositions featured on the site highlight his work as a composer of opera, chamber, orchestral, choral, theater, and dance music. Capture of the site began in February 2014. This description is based on the November 2017 capture of the site.
- Westerkamp, Hildegard, November 2017- ongoing; 1 websites in 1 archived website.
  Robots.txt (a piece of code designed to limit crawler activity within a website) was ignored. Crawl was limited to domains and subdomains of https://www.sfu.ca/~westerka/ in order to remain within the collection scope and data constraints.
  The website contains a biography of the artist, information about her compositions and projects, examples of her prose works, a discography of her published albums, and a calendar of her events. The compositions featured on the site highlight her work a pianist, flute player, and composer of music making extensive use of different acoustic environments and soundscapes. Capture of the site began in November 2017. This description is based on the November 2017 capture of the site.
- Winslow, Conrad, February 2014-ongoing; cuid5911; 5 websites in 1 archived website
  Crawl was limited to domains and subdomains of http://www.conradwinslow.com/ in order to remain within the collection scope and data constraints.
  The website contains a biography of the artist, a list of his works, audio files, and a calendar of his events. Winslow composes solo, chamber, and orchestral music. Capture of the site began in June 2017. This description is based on the June 2017 capture of the site.
- Wold, Erling, April 2014- ongoing; 2 websites in 2 archived website.
  Robots.txt (a piece of code designed to limit crawler activity within a website) was ignored. Crawl was limited to domains and subdomains of http://www.erlingwold.com/ in order to remain within the collection scope and data constraints.
  The website contains a biography of the artist, information about his compositions and projects, excerpts of reviews of his works, his blog, interviews with Wold, a gallery of images of the artist, and examples of his works in the form of embedded audio and video files. The compositions featured on the site highlight his work as a composer of large dramatic works, particularly operas, as well as chamber and solo piano pieces. He is also a noted composer of computer music. Capture of the site began in April 2014. This description is based on the October 2017 capture of the site.
- Wolfe, Julia, December 2015- ongoing; cuid5932; 1 websites in 1 archived website
  Crawl was limited to domains and subdomains of http://juliawolfemusic.com/ in order to remain within the collection scope and data constraints.
  The website contains a biography of the artist, a list of her works, news related to her music, contact information, and a calendar of her events. Wolfe's music incorporates classical, rock,and folk influences into her compositions for singers and instruments, meant for ensembles ranging from quartets to full orchestras. Capture of the site began in May 2014. This description is based on the June 2017 capture of the site.
- Wollschleger, Scott, December 2015- ongoing; cuid5938; 3 websites in 1 archived website
  Crawl was limited to domains and subdomains of http://scottwollschleger.com/ in order to remain within the collection scope and data constraints.
  Embedded Youtube video files and Soundcloud audio files on the site were captured, but do not render in the archived copy. Future changes to the Wayback Machine may allow the files to be played.
  The website contains a biography of the artist, a list of his works, news articles related to his work, and a list of upcoming events. Wollschleger's music, composed for large ensembles and chamber groups as well as solo and duo artists and instruments, explores themes of art in dystopia, the conceptualization of silence, synesthesia, and creative repetition in form. Capture of the site began in February 2014. This description is based on the July 2017 capture of the site.
- Wubbels, Eric, February 2015-ongoing; 2 websites in 2 archived websites.
  Eric Wubbels (b.1980) is a composer and pianist, and a Co-Director of the Wet Ink Ensemble. The website contains tour dates, events, recordings, videos, and scores. Also includes his work, Axamer Folio, a modular network of 24 pieces for saxophone and drumset, with no pre-set order, form, or duration.
  New crawls are accrued annually.
  Robots.txt (a piece of code designed to limit crawler activity within a website) was ignored. Crawl was limited to domains and subdomains of wubbelsmusic.com in order to remain within the collection scope and data constraints.
- Young, Katherine, April 2014- ongoing; 1 websites in 1 archived website.
  Robots.txt (a piece of code designed to limit crawler activity within a website) was ignored. Crawl was limited to domains and subdomains of http://www.katherineyoung.info/ in order to remain within the collection scope and data constraints.
  Audio and video files were not captured due to technological constraints.
  The website contains a biography of the artist, information about her compositions and projects, a calendar of her events, her blog, a gallery of images of the artist, a discography of her published albums, and examples of her works in the form of embedded audio and video files. The compositions featured on the site highlight her work as a bassonist and composer of electro-acoustic music that features improvisation. Capture of the site began in April 2014. This description is based on the December 2017 capture of the site.
- Young, Nina C., February 2015- ongoing; 1 websites in 1 archived website.
  The website contains a biography of the artist, information about her compositions and projects, a calendar of her events, a catalog of her works, press and news relating to the artist and her compositions, a gallery of images of the artist, and examples of her works in the form of embedded audio files. The compositions featured on the site highlight her work as a composer of electronic, vocal, and acoustic music for large and small ensemble performance, and for soloists and duos. Capture of the site began in February 2015. This description is based on the October 2017 capture of the site.